A Guide to the Russell Sage Foundation records FA015
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Russell Sage Foundation records, 1974-2002; 2; 120 Cubic Feet 252 document boxes.
  - Quantitative Research Synthesis, 1959-1994; 9; 3.5 Cubic Feet
    - Meeting, Decisions and Suggestions, 1988 December 8, 1988-1989 (Box 220, Folder 1682)
    - Meeting, Decisions and Suggestions, 1989 May 23 (Box 220, Folder 1683)
    - Meeting (I), 1989 May 23 (Box 220, Folder 1684)
    - Meeting (I), 1989 May 23 (Box 220, Folder 1684A)
    - Meeting (II), 1989 May 23 (Box 221, Folder 1685)
    - Meeting, Decisions and Suggestions, 1989 May 23 (Box 221, Folder 1686)
    - Meeting, Decisions and Suggestions, 1989 May 23 (Box 221, Folder 1686A)
    - Meeting, 1993 May 23, 1988-1989 (Box 221, Folder 1687)
    - Meeting, 1989 November 2, 1983, 1985-1986, 1989 (Box 221, Folder 1688)
    - Meeting, 1989 November 2 (Box 221, Folder 1689)
    - Meeting, 1990 March 15 (Box 221, Folder 1690)
    - Meeting, 1990 June 20 (Box 221, Folder 1691)
    - Meeting, 1991 January 18, 1988-1991 (Box 222, Folder 1692)
    - Meeting, 1991 January 18, 1988-1991 (Box 222, Folder 1692A)
    - Meeting, 1991 January 18, 1990-1991 (Box 222, Folder 1693)
    - Meeting, 1991 January 18, 1990-1991 (Box 222, Folder 1693A)
    - Meeting, 1991 May 9-10, 1983-1985, 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 222, Folder 1694)
    - Meeting, 1991 May 9-10, 1983-1985, 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 222, Folder 1694A)
    - Meeting, 1991 December 12, 1980-1984, 1990-1992 (Box 222, Folder 1695)
    - Meeting, 1991 December 12, 1980-1984, 1990-1992 (Box 222, Folder 1695A)
    - Meeting, 1992 May 4, Upcoming Meeting (Box 223, Folder 1696)
    - Meeting, 1992 May 4 (I), 1978-1992 (Box 223, Folder 1697)
    - Meeting, 1992 May 4 (II), 1978-1992 (Box 223, Folder 1698)
    - Meeting, 1992 May 4 (II), 1978-1992 (Box 223, Folder 1698A)
    - Meeting, 1992 December 5 (Box 223, Folder 1699)
    - Meeting, 1993 May 25 (Box 223, Folder 1700)
    - Meeting, 1993 December 3 (Box 223, Folder 1701)
    - Meta-Analysis, Curriculum Vitae, 1986 (Box 223, Folder 1702)
    - Meta-Analysis, Curriculum Vitae, 1986 (Box 223, Folder 1702A)
    - Meta-Analysis, Notes, 1985 (Box 223, Folder 1703)
    - Meta-Analysis, Reprints, 1983 & 1986-1988 (Box 223, Folder 1704)
    - Meta-Analysis Meeting, 1986 September 18 (Box 223, Folder 1705, Folder 1702)
    - Meta-Analysis Meeting, 1987 February 24, 1986-1987 (Box 223, Folder 1706)
    - Meta-Analysis Meeting, 1987 February 24, 1986-1987 (Box 223, Folder 1706A)
    - Mosteller, Frederick, 1986-1991 (Box 223, Folder 1707)
    - Mosteller, Frederick, Problem Formulation, 1989-1990 (Box 223, Folder 1708)
    - Nominations, 1983 & 1986-1987 (Box 224, Folder 1709)
    - Nominations, 1983 & 1986-1987 (Box 224, Folder 1709A)
    - Program Activities Report, 1992 (Box 224, Folder 1710)
    - Rosenthal, Robert, 1986 (Box 224, Folder 1711)
    - Sample Meta-Analysis, 1987 (Box 224, Folder 1712)
    - Scholarly Publishing on the Electronic Networks, 1992 (Box 224, Folder 1713)
    - Smith, V. Kerry, 1988 & 1990 (Box 224, Folder 1714)
    - Sub-Committees, 1987-1988 (Box 224, Folder 1715)
    - Sub-Committees, 1987-1988 (Box 224, Folder 1715A)
    - Wortman, Paul, 1986-1987 (Box 224, Folder 1716)
    - Wortman, Paul, 1986-1987 (Box 224, Folder 1716A)
  - Economic Sociology, 1990-1992; 10; 1.75 Cubic Feet
    - Economic Sociology, 1990-1992 (Box 224, Folder 1717)
    - Economic Sociology Seminar, 1990 (Box 224, Folder 1718)
    - Economic Sociology Seminar, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 1719)
    - Economic Sociology Seminar, 1991 January 18 (Box 224, Folder 1720)
    - Economic Sociology Seminar, 1991 February 8 (Box 225, Folder 1721)
    - Economic Sociology Seminar, 1991 March 8 (Box 225, Folder 1722)
    - Economic Sociology Seminar, 1991 April 5 (Box 225, Folder 1723)
    - Economic Sociology Seminar, 1991 May 10 (Box 225, Folder 1724)
    - Economic Sociology Seminar, 1991 June 4 (Box 225, Folder 1725)
    - Economic Sociology Seminar, 1991 October 24 (Box 225, Folder 1726)
    - Economic Sociology Seminar, 1991 Novmeber 22 (Box 225, Folder 1727)
    - Economic Sociology Seminar, 1991 December 19 (Box 225, Folder 1728)
    - Economic Sociology Seminar, 1992 March 20 (Box 225, Folder 1729)
    - Economic Sociology Working Group, 1990 November 16 (Box 226, Folder 1730)
    - Economic Sociology Working Group, 1990 December 14 (Box 226, Folder 1731)
    - Economic Sociology Working Group, 1991-1992 (Box 226, Folder 1732)
    - Economic Sociology Working Group, 1992 January 31 (Box 226, Folder 1733)
    - Economic Sociology Working Group, 1992 February 28 (Box 226, Folder 1734)
    - Economic Sociology Working Group, 1992 April 27 (Box 226, Folder 1735)
    - Economic Sociology Working Group, 1992 May 18 (Box 226, Folder 1736)
    - Economic Sociology Working Group, 1992 June 12 (Box 226, Folder 1737)
    - Economic Sociology Working Group, Gerlach, Michael, 1992 June 12 (Box 227, Folder 1738)
    - Behavioral Economic Session (Trust), 1992 (Box 227, Folder 1739)
    - Memoranda, 1991 (Box 227, Folder 1740)
    - Program Prososal, Granovetter, Mark, 1992 (Box 227, Folder 1741)
    - Sabel, Chalres, Moebius Strip, 1991 (Box 227, Folder 1742)
    - Sabel, Charles, Moebius Strip, 1991 (Box 227, Folder 1742A)
    - Swedberg, Richard, Exploration in Economic Sociology, 1991 (Box 227, Folder 1743)
  - Multi-City Survey of Urban Inequality (MCSUI), 1991-1999; 11; 2.7 Cubic Feet
    - Advisory Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 227, Folder 1744)
    - Analysis Plan, 1993 April 30 Version, 1992-1994 (Box 227, Folder 1745)
    - Analysis Plan & Questionnaire, 1992-1993 (Box 227, Folder 1746)
    - Ann Arbor Visit, 1992 January 17 (Box 227, Folder 1747)
    - Asian Interview Sample, Greater Boston, 1992 (Box 227, Folder 1748)
    - Atlanta, 1992-1994 (Box 228, Folder 1749)
    - Bibliography, 1996 October 1 (Box 228, Folder 1750)
    - Boston Trip, 1995 May 15 (Box 228, Folder 1751)
    - Boston Trip, 1995 May 15 (Box 228, Folder 1751A)
    - Budget & Cost Sharing, Ford Foundation, Social Science Research Council and Alice O'Connor, 1993-1994 (Box 228, Folder 1752)
    - Conference at Russell Sage Foundation (I), 1995 September 28-30 (Box 228, Folder 1753)
    - Conference at Russell Sage Foundation (II), 1995 Spetember 28-30 (Box 228, Folder 1754)
    - Conference at Russell Sage Foundation (I), 1996 May 31 (Box 229, Folder 1755)
    - Conference at Russell Sage Foundation (II), 1996 May 31 (Box 229, Folder 1756)
    - Conference at Russell Sage Foundation, 1996 December 13-14 (Box 229, Folder 1757)
    - Conference Call, 1994 November 30 (Box 229, Folder 1758)
    - Conferences, 1995-1996 (Box 229, Folder 1759)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1996 (Box 229, Folder 1760)
    - Cost Sharing, Ford Foundation/Russell Sage Foundation, 1994 (Box 229, Folder 1761)
    - Cost Sharing, Kubisch, Anne, 1994 (Box 229, Folder 1762)
    - Data Coordinator (I), 1996 September 4 (Box 230, Folder 1763)
    - Data Coordinator (II), 1996 September 4 (Box 230, Folder 1764)
    - Detroit, 1992 (Box 230, Folder 1765)
    - Detroit Area Study-1992 (I), 1992-1994 (Box 230, Folder 1766)
    - Detroit Area Study-1992 (II), 1992-1994 (Box 230, Folder 1767)
    - Employer Survey Working Group, Atlanta, 1991 (Box 231, Folder 1768)
    - George, Gary R., Milwaukee, 1991 (Box 231, Folder 1769)
    - Howard Heinz Endowment, Wishart, Alfred W., 1991 (Box 231, Folder 1770)
    - Intinerary to Ann Arbor, 1992 (Box 231, Folder 1771)
    - Intinerary to Ann Arbor, 1992 (Box 231, Folder 1171A)
    - Los Angeles Group, 1991-1992 (Box 231, Folder 1772)
    - Los Angeles Group, 1991-1992 (Box 231, Folder 1772A)
    - Los Angeles Manuscript, 1998-1999 (Box 231, Folder 1773)
    - Los Angeles Manuscript, 1998-1999 (Box 231, Folder 1773A)
    - Meeting, 1992 July 23-25 (Box 231, Folder 1774)
    - Meeting, 1994 May 7 (Box 231, Folder 1775)
    - Meeting, Minutes, 1995 February (Box 231, Folder 1776)
    - Meeting, 1996 February 8-9 (I), 1995-1996 (Box 232, Folder 1777)
    - Meeting, 1996 February 8-9 (II), 1995-1996 (Box 232, Folder 1778)
    - Meeting, Santa Barbara, 1997 March 21-22 (Box 232, Folder 1779)
    - Multi-City Survey of Urban Inequality Study Review, 1991-1992 (Box 232, Folder 1780)
    - Multi-City Survey of Urban Inequality Study Review, 1991-1992 (Box 232, Folder 1780A)
    - Multi-City Volume on Urban Inequality, 1996 (Box 232, Folder 1781)
    - Presentation to Russell Sage Foundation Board of Trustees, 1996 June (Box 232, Folder 1782)
    - Progress Report, 1996 February, 1995-1996 (Box 233, Folder 1783)
    - Project Seminar, Conference Call, 1992 March 24 (Box 233, Folder 1784)
    - Research Coordinating Committee, 1993 April 17-18 (Box 233, Folder 1785)
    - Research Coordinating Committee, Ann Arbor, 1993 July 27 (Box 233, Folder 1786)
    - Research Coordinating Committee, Conference Call, Decisions & Responsiblities, 1994 November 4 (Box 233, Folder 1787)
    - Research Coordinating Committee Proceedings, 1995 February 3-4 (Box 233, Folder 1788)
    - Roster, 1995 October (Box 233, Folder 1789)
    - Roster, 1996 October (Box 233, Folder 1890)
    - Seminar, 1992 July 23-25 (Box 233, Folder 1791)
    - Seminar, University of California, Los Angeles, Minutes, 1992 October 16-17 (Box 233, Folder 1792)
    - Social Science Research Council, 1993 (Box 233, Folder 1793)
    - Social Science Research Coucil, Correspondence, 1993 (Box 233, Folder 1794)
    - Social Science Research Council-Ford Foundation Proposal, 1992 (Box 233, Folder 1795)
    - Survey Requests, undated (Box 233, Folder 1796)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, Budget, 1992 (Box 233, Folder 1797)
  - Publications, 1921-2000; 12; 14.4 Cubic Feet
    - Audit Report-1969-1970, 1970-1971 (Box 234, Folder 1798)
    - Publication Department Reports, 1921-1930 (Box 234, Folder 1799)
    - Publication Department Reports, 1930-1942 (Box 234, Folder 1800)
    - Publication Department Reports, 1942-1949 (Box 234, Folder 1801)
    - Publications Report, 1943-revised 1952 April 30 (Box 234, Folder 1802)
    - Publication Department Reports, 1949-1960 (Box 234, Folder 1803)
    - Publications Report, 1950-1951 (Box 234, Folder 1804)
    - Publications Report, 1951-1952 (Box 234, Folder 1805)
    - Publications Report, 1952-1953 (Box 235, Folder 1806)
    - Publications Report, 1953-1954 (Box 235, Folder 1807)
    - Publications Report, 1954-1955 (Box 235, Folder 1808)
    - Publications Report, 1955-1956 (Box 235, Folder 1809)
    - Publications Report, 1956-1957 (Box 235, Folder 1810)
    - Publications Report, 1957-1958 (Box 235, Folder 1811)
    - Publications Report, 1958-1959 (Box 235, Folder 1812)
    - Publications Report, 1959-1960 (Box 235, Folder 1813)
    - Publications Report, 1960-1961 (Box 235, Folder 1814)
    - Publications Report, 1961-1962 (Box 235, Folder 1815)
    - Publications Report, 1962-1963 (Box 235, Folder 1816)
    - Publications Report, 1963-1964 (Box 235, Folder 1817)
    - Publications Report, 1964-1965 (Box 235, Folder 1818)
    - Publications Report, 1965-1966 (Box 235, Folder 1819)
    - Publications Report, 1966-1967 (Box 235, Folder 1820)
    - Publications Report, 1967-1968 (Box 235, Folder 1821)
    - Publications Report, 1968-1969 (Box 236, Folder 1822)
    - Publications Report, 1969-1970 (Box 236, Folder 1823)
    - Publications Report, 1973-1974 (Box 236, Folder 1824)
    - Publications Report, 1974-1975 (Box 236, Folder 1825)
    - Year End Report, 1974-1975 (Box 236, Folder 1826)
    - Year End Report, 1975-1976 (Box 236, Folder 1827)
    - Books, Reserve Stock, 1950-1968 (Box 236, Folder 1828)
    - Inventory, 1968-1969 (Box 236, Folder 1829)
    - Publications Department, Authors-Titles-Publication Dates, 1908-1979 (Box 236, Folder 1830)
    - Communication, Press Coverage for Russell Sage Foundation Books, 1987-1989 (Box 236, Folder 1831)
    - Adams, John S., Census, Production, 1988 (Box 236, Folder 1832)
    - Adams, John S., Housing America, Book Reviews, 1988-1990 (Box 236, Folder 1833)
    - Alonso, William and Paul Starr, The Politics of Numbers, 1987-1989 (Box 236, Folder 1834)
    - Alonso, William and Paul Starr, The Politics of Numbers, Book Reviews, 1987-1989 (Box 236, Folder 1835)
    - Alonso, William and Paul Starr, The Politics of Numbers, Census, Production, 1986 (Box 236, Folder 1836)
    - Andrews, F. Emerson, Philanthropic Foundations, 1973 & 1977 (Box 236, Folder 1837)
    - Armor, David J., The American School Counselor, Book Reviews, 1969-1970 (Box 236, Folder 1838)
    - Back, Kurt W., Beyond Words: The Story of Sensitivity Training and the Encounter Movement, Book Reviews, 1972-1973 (Box 236, Folder 1839)
    - Back, Kurt W., Beyond Words: The Story of Sensitivity Training and the Encounter Movement, Permissions, 1975 (Box 236, Folder 1840)
    - Back, Kurt W., Beyond Words: The Story of Sensitivity Training and the Encounter Movement, Subsidiary Rights, 1972-1973 (Box 236, Folder 1841)
    - Balbus, Isaac D., The Dialectics of Legal Repression, Book Reviews, 1975-1981 (Box 236, Folder 1842)
    - Balbus, Isaac D., The Dialectics of Legal Repression, Production, 1972 (Box 236, Folder 1843)
    - Balbus, Isaac D., The Dialectics of Legal Repression, Subsidiary Rights, 1976 (Box 236, Folder 1844)
    - Balk, Alfred, The List: Property Without Taxes, Book Reviews, 1971 (Box 236, Folder 1845)
    - Barber, Bernard A., Drugs and Society, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 237, Folder 1846)
    - Barber, Bernard A., Effective Social Science: Eight Cases in Economics, Political Science and Sociology, Book Reviews, 1988-1990 (Box 237, Folder 1847)
    - Barber, Bernard A., Effective Social Science: Eight Cases in Economics, Political Science and Sociology, Production, undated (Box 237, Folder 1848)
    - Barber, Bernard A., Research on Human Subjects, Book Reviews, 1973-1976 (Box 237, Folder 1849)
    - Barber, Bernard A., Research on Human Subjects, Production, 1972 (Box 237, Folder 1850)
    - Barber, Bernard A., Research on Human Subjects, Subsidiary Rights, 1976-1977 (Box 237, Folder 1851)
    - Barringer, Herbert R., Asian and Pacific Islanders in the United States, Production, 1995 (Box 237, Folder 1852)
    - Barringer, Herbert R., Robert W. Gardner, and Michael J. Levin, Asians and Pacific Islanders in the United States, Booke Reviews, 1994 (Box 237, Folder 1853)
    - Barringer, Herbert R., Robert W. Gardner, and Michael J. Levin, Asians and Pacific Islanders in the United States, Contract, 1991 (Box 237, Folder 1854)
    - Barringer, Herbert R., Robert W. Gardner, and Michael J. Levin, Asians and Pacific Islanders in the United States, Contract, 1991 (Box 237, Folder 1854A)
    - Barringer, Herbert R., Robert W. Gardner, and Michael J. Levin, Asians and Pacific Islanders in the United States, Production, 1991-1993 (Box 237, Folder 1855)
    - Bauer, Raymond A. and Dan H. Fenn, Jr., The Corporate Social Audit, Book Reviews, 1972-1974 (Box 237, Folder 1856)
    - Bauer, Raymond A. and Dan H. Fenn, Jr., The Corporate Social Audit, Subsidiary Rights, 1973-1979 (Box 237, Folder 1857)
    - Bell, Wendell and James A. Mau, The Sociology of the Future: Theory, Cases, and Annotated Bibliography, Book Reviews, 1972 (Box 237, Folder 1858)
    - Bell, Wendell and James A. Mau, The Sociology of the Future: Theory, Cases, and Annotated Bibliography, Production, 1970 (Box 237, Folder 1859)
    - Bender, Thomas and Carl E. Schorske, Budapest and New York: Studies in Metropolitan Transformation, 1870-1930, Book Reviews, 1994-1996 (Box 237, Folder 1860)
    - Bender, Thomas and Carl E. Schorske, Budapest and New York: Studies in Metropolitan Transformation, 1870-1930, Foriegn, 1994 (Box 237, Folder 1861)
    - Bender, Thomas and Carl E. Schorske, Budapest and New York: Studies in Metropolitan Transformation, 1870-1930, Photographs, undated (Box 237, Folder 1862)
    - Bender, Thomas and Carl E. Schorske, Budapest and New York: Studies in Metropolitan Transformation, 1870-1930, Preliminary, 1991 (Box 237, Folder 1863)
    - Bender, Thomas and Carl E. Schorske, Budapest and New York: Studies in Metropolitan Transformation, 1870-1930, Production, 1992-1993 (Box 237, Folder 1864)
    - Benjamin, Gerald and Charles Brecher, The Two New Yorks, Book Reviews, 1989-1990 (Box 237, Folder 1865)
    - Benjamin, Gerald and Charles Brecher, The Two New Yorks, Production, 1988 (Box 237, Folder 1866)
    - Berke, Joel S., Margaret E. Goertz, and Richard J. Coley, Politicans, Judges and City Schools, Book Reviews, 1985-1986 (Box 237, Folder 1867)
    - Berke, Joel S., Margaret E. Goertz, and Richard J. Coley, Politicans, Judges and City Schools, Production, undated (Box 237, Folder 1868)
    - Bernstein, Ilene and Howard Freeman, Academic and Entrepreneurial Research: The Consequences of Diversity in Federal Evaluation Studies, Book Reviews, 1975-1977 (Box 237, Folder 1869)
    - Bernstein, Ilene and Howard Freeman, Academic and Entrepreneurial Research: The Consequences of Diversity in Federal Evaluation Studies, Production, undated (Box 237, Folder 1870)
    - Bianchi, Suzanne M. and Daphne Spain, American Women in Transition, Book Reviews, 1986-1991 (Box 237, Folder 1871)
    - Bianchi, Suzanne M. and Daphne Spain, American Women in Transition, Census, undated (Box 237, Folder 1872)
    - Bienen, Henry, The Military Intervenes: Case Study in Political Development, Book Reviews, 1968-1972 (Box 237, Folder 1873)
    - Borgatta, Edgar F., David Fanshel, and Henry J. Meyers, Social Workers' Preceptions of Clients, Subsidiary RIghts, 1980 (Box 237, Folder 1874)
    - Brim, Orville G., Jr., Howard E. Freeman, Sol Levine, and Norman A. Scotch, The Dying Patient, Book Reviews, 1970-1977 (Box 237, Folder 1875)
    - Brim, Orville G., Jr., Howard E. Freeman, Sol Levine, and Norman A. Scotch, The Dying Patient, Permissions, 1968-1969 (Box 237, Folder 1876)
    - Brim, Orville G., Jr., Howard E. Freeman, Sol Levine, and Norman A. Scotch, The Dying Patient, Subsidiary Rights, 1968-1971 & 1977 (Box 237, Folder 1877)
    - Brim, Orville G., Jr., David C. Glass, John Neulinger, and Ira J. Firestone, Americna Beliefs and Attitiudes About Intelligence, Book Reviews, 1969-1972 (Box 237, Folder 1878)
    - Bronfenbrenner, Urie, Two Worlds of Childhood, U.S. and U.S.S.R., Book Reviews, 1970-1974 (Box 238, Folder 1879)
    - Bronfenbrenner, Urie, Two Worlds of Childhood, U.S. and U.S.S.R., Simon & Schuster Inc., 1970-1981 (Box 238, Folder 1880)
    - Bronfenbrenner, Urie, Two Worlds of Childhood, U.S. and U.S.S.R., Contract, Simon & Schuster Paperback, 1971 (Box 238, Folder 1881)
    - Bronfenbrenner, Urie, Two Worlds of Childhood, U.S. and U.S.S.R., Permissions, 1969-1980 (Box 238, Folder 1882)
    - Bronfenbrenner, Urie, Two Worlds of Childhood, U.S. and U.S.S.R., Subsidiary Rights, 1970-1973 & 1980-1984 (Box 238, Folder 1883)
    - Brown, Esther Lucile, Newer Dimensions of Patient Care, Part III, Permissions, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 1884)
    - Brown, Esther Lucile, Newer Dimensions of Patient Care, Part III, Subsidiary Rights, 1964-1966 & 1976 (Box 238, Folder 1885)
    - Brown, Esther Lucile, Nursing of the Future, Subsidiary Rights, 1965-1967 (Box 238, Folder 1886)
    - Brown, Michael K., Working the Streets: Police Discretion and the Dilemmas of Reform, Books Reviews, 1981-1982 (Box 238, Folder 1887)
    - Brown, Michael K., Working the Streets: Police Discretion and the Dilemmas of Reform, Books Reviews, 1981-1985 (Box 238, Folder 1888)
    - Brown, Michael K., Working the Streets: Police Discretion and the Dilemmas of Reform, Production, 1981 (Box 238, Folder 1889)
    - Brown, Michael K., Working the Streets: Police Discretion and the Dilemmas of Reform-Reprint, Book Reviews, 1988 (Box 238, Folder 1890)
    - Brown, Michael K., Working the Streets: Police Discretion and the Dilemmas of Reform, Paperback Reprint, 1990 (Box 238, Folder 1891)
    - Bumpass, Larry L. and James A. Sweet, American Families and Households, Book Reviews, 1988-1991 (Box 238, Folder 1892)
    - Bumpass, Larry L. and James A. Sweet, American Families and Households, Production, 1990 (Box 238, Folder 1893)
    - Burke, John P. and Fred I. Greenstein, How Presidents Test Reality: Decisions on Vietman, 1954 and 1965, Book Reviews, 1989-1993 (Box 238, Folder 1894)
    - Burke, John P. and Fred I. Greenstein, How Presidents Test Reality: Decisions on Vietman, 1954 and 1965, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1990 (Box 238, Folder 1895)
    - Burt, Martha R., Over the Edge: The Growth of Homelessness in the 1980's, Book Reviews, 1991-1994 (Box 238, Folder 1896)
    - Burt, Martha R., Over the Edge: The Growth of Homelessness in the 1980's, Design, 1990 (Box 238, Folder 1897)
    - Burt, Martha R., Over the Edge: The Growth of Homelessness in the 1980's, Prelinimary, 1990 (Box 238, Folder 1898)
    - Burt, Martha R., Over the Edge: The Growth of Homelessness in the 1980's, Production, 1991 (Box 238, Folder 1899)
    - Byington, Margaret, Homestead: The Households of Mill Town, Subsidiary Rights, 1973-1974 & 1979 (Box 238, Folder 1900)
    - Campbell, Angus, Philip E. Converse, and Williard L. Rodgers, The Quality of American Life, Perceptions, Evaluations and Satisfactions, Book Reviews, 1976-1977 (Box 239, Folder 1901)
    - Campbell, Angus, Philip E. Converse, and Williard L. Rodgers, The Quality of American Life, Perceptions, Evaluations and Satisfactions, Production, 1975 (Box 239, Folder 1902)
    - Campbell, Angus, Philip E. Converse, and Williard L. Rodgers, The Quality of American Life, Perceptions, Evaluations and Satisfactions, Reviews and Free Copies, 1978 (Box 239, Folder 1903)
    - Carden, Maren Lockwood, The New Feminist Movement, Book Reviews, 1974-1975 (Box 239, Folder 1904)
    - Carden, Maren Lockwood, The New Feminist Movement, Subsidiary Rights, 1974 (Box 239, Folder 1905)
    - Carlin, Jerome E., Lawyers' Ethics: A Survey of the New York City Bar, Book Reviews, 1966-1971 (Box 239, Folder 1906)
    - Carlin, Jerome E., Lawyers' Ethics: A Survey of the New York City Bar, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 239, Folder 1907)
    - Carlin, Jerome E., Lawyers' Ethics: A Survey of the New York City Bar, Subsidiary RIghts, 1974 & 1982 (Box 239, Folder 1908)
    - Carlin, Jerome E., Jan Howard, and Sheldon L. Messinger, Civil Justice and the Poor, Book Reviews, 1969 (Box 239, Folder 1909)
    - Caro, Francis G., Reading in Evaluation Research, Book Reviews, 1971-1972 & 1978-1980 (Box 239, Folder 1910)
    - Caro, Francis G., Reading in Evaluation Research, Permissions-First Edition, 1970-1971 (Box 239, Folder 1911)
    - Caro, Francis G., Reading in Evaluation Research, Permissions-Second Edition, 1976-1977 (Box 239, Folder 1912)
    - Carter, Douglass and Stephen Strickland, TV Violence and the Child, Book Reviews, 1975-1977 (Box 239, Folder 1913)
    - Carter, Douglass and Stephen Strickland, TV Violence and the Child, Production, 1974 (Box 239, Folder 1914)
    - Census 1985, General Production (Box 239, Folder 1915)
    - Chamberlain, Mariam, Women in Academe; Progress and Prospects, Book Reviews, 1989-1991 (Box 239, Folder 1916)
    - Chamberlain, Mariam, Women in Academe; Progress and Prospects, Production, 1988 (Box 239, Folder 1917)
    - Chamberlain, Mariam, Women in Academe; Progress and Prospects, Production & Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 239, Folder 1918)
    - Coleman, James S. and Siegwart Lindenberg, Approaches to Social Theory, Book Reviews, 1986 (Box 239, Folder 1919)
    - Coleman, James S. and Siegwart Lindenberg, Approaches to Social Theory, Production, 1985 (Box 239, Folder 1920)
    - Consortium of Social Science Association (COSSA)/The American Political Science Association (APSA), Guide to Federal Funding of Social Scienctists, Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 239, Folder 1921)